<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Yantra Homes</title>
<link>https://www.yantrahomes.co.uk</link>
<description>Latest Property for sale in Bulgaria from Yantra Homes – Veliko Tarnovo</description>
<pubDate>February 22, 2024</pubDate>
<image>
<url>https://www.yantrahomes.co.uk/yantrahomes.ico</url>
<link>https://www.yantrahomes.co.uk/en/home</link>
</image>
<item>
<title>House for sale in Mihaltsi, Pavlikeni Municipality, Price 44950 EUR</title>
<link>https://www.yantrahomes.co.uk/en/property-House-for-sale-Mihaltsi-Pavlikeni/id/5248054</link>
<description>
<![CDATA[ <img title="" src="https://files.yantrahomes.com/thumbs_active/48/thumb_99653.jpg" alt="" width="200" height="150" /><br/> ]]>
2024-02-16 17:11:51 <p>Nestled in a picturesque wine-growing region, Mihaltsi is a fully-serviced village with year-round access to major roads, a church, a town hall, stores, a school, pubs, and a community centre. This community is in a wonderful location, approximately 8 kilometres from the town of Pavlikeni, 24 km from Veliko Tarnovo, and close to the main road that runs from Sofia to Varna.</p> <p>&nbsp;</p> <p>This lovely property borders wide open countryside and can be found at the end of a quiet street at the edge of the village.</p> <p>&nbsp;</p> <p>The garden is large and flat. It is partially fenced and has been completely plowed in preparation for planting vegetables, but it could also be manicured to create a conventionally landscaped garden.</p> <p>&nbsp;</p> <p>The house is partially renovated. The current owners completed the works to an exceptionally high standard. New UPVC windows and doors have been installed throughout. Modern materials have been used to insulate the exterior of the walls, and the house has been completely rewired and has new plumbing on both levels.</p> <p>&nbsp;</p> <p>The house boasts a newly renovated shower room on the lower level and a sleek, contemporary-fitted kitchen with a built-in electric oven with hob and plenty of storage space. There is a further room on the ground floor that can be used as a study, bedroom, or small living room.</p> <p>&nbsp;</p> <p>At the moment, two of the bedrooms on the upper floor are being used. Another room has the plumbing set up to become a family bathroom, but it might alternatively serve as an additional bedroom. There are also stairs here that give access to a large loft area that can be used for additional storage or converted to provide further living accommodations.</p> <p>&nbsp;</p> <p>Adjacent to the main house is a large annex; the windows have been replaced with UPVC units. With further renovations, it could become a large living room, perhaps a recreation room, or guest accommodation.</p> <p>&nbsp;</p> <p>Outside, there are many other buildings in use; they include a utility room with a functional bread oven and internal laundry room and shower, a summer kitchen with new electrics and plumbing, a shipping container in a fixed position for secure storage, and a barn of around 60 square metres.</p> <p>&nbsp;</p> <p>The garden can be accessed through large double gates, where there is ample space and hard-standing for many vehicles. The garden is enclosed with a wire fence, and there is a water well with a pump system for garden irrigation.</p> <p>&nbsp;</p> <p>If you are searching for a safe haven where limitless possibilities await and promise a life in harmony with nature, this could be the solution that you are seeking.</p>
</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>House for sale in Burya, Sevlievo Municipality, Price 29995 EUR</title>
<link>https://www.yantrahomes.co.uk/en/property-House-for-sale-Burya-Sevlievo/id/5425037</link>
<description>
<![CDATA[ <img title="" src="https://files.yantrahomes.com/thumbs_active/47/thumb_99569.jpg" alt="" width="200" height="150" /><br/> ]]>
2023-10-03 19:30:05 <p>Located in the village of Burya, about 35 kilometres from Veliko Tarnovo, 25 kilometres from Gabrovo, and 20 kilometres from Sevlievo town.</p> <p>&nbsp;</p> <p>The property boasts a 1,532 square metre private garden with fertile soil, numerous fruit trees and a water well that has never been known to run dry. A driveway is available for off-road parking as well.</p> <p>&nbsp;</p> <p>Although the house needs work, it is generally sound, and the roof is in good shape. The ceilings on both floors are a fair height. Two big rooms that might be converted into a kitchen-diner and living room are located in a large hallway on the lower floor. The upper level features concrete stairs that lead to a big corridor, two additional rooms that may be made into bedrooms, and a storage room that is perfect for being turned into an internal shower room. There is a huge roof patio with an east facing door, as well as a south facing terrace.</p> <p>&nbsp;</p> <p>The summer kitchen has a decent roof, a basement, and is 35 square metres, so it may simply be changed to provide more living space.</p> <p>&nbsp;</p> <p>There are two sizable stone barns on the property, one of which has two stories. For any application the future owner might think of, the barns combined 85 square metres are available. On the site, there are additional storage rooms and animal shelters.</p> <p>&nbsp;</p> <p>The opportunity to develop this property however the new owners see fit is fantastic. The home is sound and in a reasonable state for habitation. A lot more living space could be created by repurposing the stone barns and summer kitchen. A viewing is advised to fully appreciate this amazing property potential</p>
</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>House for sale in Strahilovo, Polski Trambesh Municipality, Price 85000 EUR</title>
<link>https://www.yantrahomes.co.uk/en/property-House-for-sale-Strahilovo-Polski-Trambesh/id/5190041</link>
<description>
<![CDATA[ <img title="" src="https://files.yantrahomes.com/thumbs_active/46/thumb_99529.jpg" alt="" width="200" height="150" /><br/> ]]>
2023-10-03 18:33:22 <p>This lovely home has been recently refurbished, and it is situated in a bustling community with great opportunities for biking, walking, fishing, and hunting. It has efficient&nbsp;connections by bus to the nearby towns of Svishtov and Polski Trambesh. The community has great connections by road to the major towns of Veliko Tarnovo and Ruse as well as fast links to Pleven and Varna thanks to its proximity to the main motorway.</p> <p>&nbsp;</p> <p>The house is located at the end of a lane that connects to open space with a variety of pathways for exploration. Excellent privacy is provided&nbsp;to the house, which also includes a 2,330 square metre garden. The southern garden is accessible through imposing gates where there is off-street parking for cars. Most of the area is covered in lawn, with flower and plant borders. The majority of the garden is located behind the home, it is nearly flat and ideal for growing vegetables or housing animals.</p> <p>&nbsp;</p> <p>The property is easily accessible because it is all on one level and has only a few internal stairs. Additionally, every room faces south and has sizable double glazed windows.</p> <p>&nbsp;</p> <p>The present owners have rebuilt the entire house to a high standard, including new plumbing and electrical systems throughout, exterior and interior insulation, replacement PVC double-glazed windows, and more. A front door in the English cottage style serves as the primary entrance and leads into a hospitable hallway. Here you will also find the master bedroom and a roomy, contemporary bathroom with a corner bathtub. The hallway provides access to the living room, which features a wood burner to heat all the rooms in this area, as well as a sizable cupboard for handy storage.</p> <p>&nbsp;</p> <p>There is a contemporary kitchen with built-in cabinets, a built-in oven, and numerous locations for appliances and extra storage. The dining area has its own entrance from the garden and is located right next to the kitchen. In the dining room there are numerous cabinets for practical storage and a washbasin. The next room is a compact bedroom with a contemporary en-suite shower.</p> <p>&nbsp;</p> <p>The utility room, which has a washer, freezer, and space for a dryer, has a separate entrance from the garden. The third bedroom is sizable, with a separate door, and a large, contemporary en-suite shower room. There is a sizable summer&nbsp;kitchen complete&nbsp;with plumbing and electricity. There is also a stand-alone summer house behind the house and a shed for garden storage.</p> <p>&nbsp;</p> <p>The partially furnished home is for sale. It offers the ideal blend of design, functionality, and comfort by fusing traditional charm with contemporary convenience. The property has superb insulation both inside and out, which contributes to its extremely low operating expenses. Do not pass up the chance to make this property your residence; every aspect has been carefully planned to improve your quality of life.</p>
</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>House for sale in Pavel, Polski Trambesh Municipality, Price 14990 EUR</title>
<link>https://www.yantrahomes.co.uk/en/property-House-for-sale-Pavel-Polski-Trambesh/id/5197021</link>
<description>
<![CDATA[ <img title="" src="https://files.yantrahomes.com/thumbs_active/45/thumb_99497.jpg" alt="" width="200" height="150" /><br/> ]]>
2023-08-12 05:01:38 <p>Pavel village is very conveniently located. It is just 3 km from the main road connecting Sofia and Ruse. The village also provides 3 grocery shops, 3 pubs, fishing dam, a town hall, a community centre, a school, a church, well-maintained village centre and asphalt streets. This is peaceful village with friendly locals and a great place to relocate.</p> <p>&nbsp;</p> <p>Arranged over a single floor, the house provides 120 sqm of living area. There is a big summer kitchen with storage next to the main house. The house features a hallway, kitchen/living room, 5 bedrooms, bathroom, storage and hallway. The property is with solid construction and needs minimum renovation to reveal its great potential. All rooms are airy and light.</p> <p>&nbsp;</p> <p>The garden to this property is big with size of 2350 sqm, flat and in good condition. There is a barn, sheds and a big 40 sqm garage. The fertile land lends itself to gardening, fruit and vegetable growing. The garden hosts a number of fruit trees and water-well. The property has water and electricity supply and is accessible all year round via an asphalt road.</p> <p>&nbsp;</p> <p>Pavel village is situated in the Danubian Plain, 15 km from Polski Trambesh and 20 km from Svishtov. The area of the village is hilly and provides good conditions for hunting and fishing. There are a few natural reserves and a Thracian tomb you could visit.</p>
</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>House for sale in Idilevo, Sevlievo Municipality, Price 95000 EUR</title>
<link>https://www.yantrahomes.co.uk/en/property-House-for-sale-Idilevo-Sevlievo/id/5422008</link>
<description>
<![CDATA[ <img title="" src="https://files.yantrahomes.com/thumbs_active/44/thumb_99462.jpg" alt="" width="200" height="150" /><br/> ]]>
2023-07-29 06:24:49 <p>Discover a serene escape in the heart of nature with this immaculate two-story home in the charming village of Idilevo, ideally located just 30 km from the cultural hub of Veliko Tarnovo and surrounded by breath-taking panoramic views of open forestry.</p> <p>&nbsp;</p> <p>Nestled in an idyllic landscape, this thoughtfully renovated property offers the perfect blend of rural living and modern convenience. Boasting a spacious 145 sq. m. living area, this brick-built house features an inviting open-plan living room and kitchen area on the ground floor, along with a shower room with a WC and an additional room. Upstairs, three comfortable bedrooms await, two of which lead to panoramic terraces offering mesmerising vistas. A corridor and a bathroom with a bathtub add to the functional layout, ensuring both comfort and ease.</p> <p>&nbsp;</p> <p>Step inside and experience elegance at every turn, with laminate flooring exuding sophistication and beautifully tiled finishes in the corridor, kitchen, and staircase. Adorned with UPVC double glazing, the home has PVC windows enhance both aesthetics and energy efficiency, while a grand, authentic fireplace in the living room exudes warmth and charm. Radiators in every room guarantee your comfort throughout the year.</p> <p>&nbsp;</p> <p>Spread across an expansive plot of more than 3000 sq. m., this property is a paradise for outdoor enthusiasts. Embrace the freedom to create your dream garden, host gatherings, or indulge in various activities surrounded by natures beauty. Alongside the main house, two outbuildings and a garage offer ample storage solutions and convenient parking.</p> <p>&nbsp;</p> <p>Conveniently situated just 1 km from the main road connecting Sofia and Varna, this property provides easy accessibility to renowned towns such as Veliko Tarnovo, Gabrovo, and Sevlievo. Immerse yourself in the enchanting village of Idilevo, where modern amenities and essential utilities are within reach.</p> <p>&nbsp;</p> <p>This is an exceptional opportunity to embrace the tranquillity of rural living while revelling in modern comforts and a captivating panorama. Do not miss your chance to own this fully renovated gem in the heart of Central North Bulgaria!</p> <p>&nbsp;</p>
</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>House for sale in Old Part, Veliko Tarnovo Town Municipality, Price 260000 EUR</title>
<link>https://www.yantrahomes.co.uk/en/property-House-for-sale-Old-Part-Veliko-Tarnovo-Town/id/50001262</link>
<description>
<![CDATA[ <img title="" src="https://files.yantrahomes.com/thumbs_active/42/thumb_99410.jpg" alt="" width="200" height="150" /><br/> ]]>
2023-07-28 03:34:21 <p>This cosy home is located in one of the most beautiful areas of Veliko Tarnovo, the Old Town, renowned for its Revival homes and rustic atmosphere. The area is quiet and peaceful, just minutes from the shopping streets of Veliko Tarnovo. The house is located in the heart of a historic street and is in immediate proximity to the town centre.</p> <p>&nbsp;</p> <p>The house is built over 3 floors and has total living area of 162 sqm. The ground floor comprises of a storage and Jacuzzi. An internal staircase leads to the first storey where you will find hallway, 2 bedrooms and bathroom. The last floor offers a hallway, kitchen, living room, bathroom and balcony where you can enjoy your first coffee or relax in the evening while enjoying the beautiful view. This south-facing property has a small garden that reveals great views towards the Asenevtsi Monument, Boris Denev State Art Gallery and the Sveta Gora Hill, making it a great place to relax and unwind. The house has been fully renovated and features insulation, 2 ACs, new el and plumbing system, new roof, sold fully furnished and is ready to move in.</p> <p>&nbsp;</p> <p>Just five minutes away is the main town shopping street with numerous shops, boutiques, caf&eacute;s, restaurants, bars and clubs. Or you can walk around the beautiful old town and explore its many gems such as Tsarevets Fortress where Bulgarian rulers used to live. At the same time this property allows quick and easy access to all government institutions and administrative buildings. All these characteristics make it suitable both for a year round residence and for renting out.</p>
</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>House for sale in Razsoha, Zlataritsa Municipality, Price 95000 EUR</title>
<link>https://www.yantrahomes.co.uk/en/property-House-for-sale-Razsoha-Zlataritsa/id/5089012</link>
<description>
<![CDATA[ <img title="" src="https://files.yantrahomes.com/thumbs_active/41/thumb_99407.jpg" alt="" width="200" height="150" /><br/> ]]>
2023-07-08 11:48:37 <p>Nestled in the serene mountain village of Razsoha, within the Zlataritsa municipality of Central North Bulgaria, this remarkable property presents an extraordinary opportunity. Welcome to the old school house, a true gem of the 1960s, boasting immense potential and a breath-taking backdrop of natural beauty.</p> <p>&nbsp;</p> <p>Spread across three floors, this brick-built property encompasses a generous 450 square metres of floor space. Stepping inside, you will be captivated by the authentic charm that permeates each room. The two internal staircases gracefully connect the basement to the main two floors, providing easy access throughout the building.</p> <p>&nbsp;</p> <p>The old classrooms, preserved in their original glory, offer approximately 35 square metres of space each. Complete with desks, blackboards, and educational posters adorning the walls, they exude a nostalgic ambiance that stirs the imagination.</p> <p>&nbsp;</p> <p>Outside, the expansive grounds sprawl over an impressive 13,000 square metres. The property encompasses a former football pitch, perfect for recreational activities, and landscaped gardens to the south and east. A grand driveway welcomes you, leading to ample parking facilities for numerous cars.</p> <p>&nbsp;</p> <p>In addition to the main building, a separate structure of approximately 150 square metres awaits within the grounds. Once utilized as additional classrooms and a toilet block, it currently requires attention. With a new roof and some necessary repairs, this building could be rejuvenated to complement the main property.</p> <p>&nbsp;</p> <p>Situated in the mesmerizing River Kamenitsa valley, amidst the rolling hills of the Stara Planina range, Razsoha village boasts exceptional natural beauty. The Bebrovska river, a mere 200 metres away, beckons with its abundance of fish, while the soaring eagles grace the sky, providing an awe-inspiring spectacle.</p> <p>&nbsp;</p> <p>Beyond the village, the Zlataritsa municipality, within the renowned Veliko Tarnovo district, offers a wealth of outdoor activities and scenic wonders. Explore the many walking trails, meander alongside picturesque rivers, or indulge in fishing in the nearby reservoirs, all of which are favoured by avid tourists.</p> <p>&nbsp;</p> <p>Unleash your imagination and unlock the full potential of this extraordinary property. The options for transformation are limitless. Create a captivating leisure complex, an enchanting hotel or hostel catering to walking and outdoor enthusiasts, or even a serene retirement home - the choice is yours to shape the future of this remarkable space.</p> <p>&nbsp;</p> <p>Do not miss out on this once-in-a-lifetime opportunity to own a piece of history, surrounded by stunning landscapes and endless possibilities. Contact us today to embark on your journey in Razsoha, where dreams become reality.</p>
</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>House for sale in Dolna Lipnitsa, Pavlikeni Municipality, Price 12000 EUR</title>
<link>https://www.yantrahomes.co.uk/en/property-House-for-sale-Dolna-Lipnitsa-Pavlikeni/id/5226041</link>
<description>
<![CDATA[ <img title="" src="https://files.yantrahomes.com/thumbs_active/33/thumb_99063.jpg" alt="" width="200" height="150" /><br/> ]]>
2023-06-06 19:03:18 <p>The village of Dolna Lipnitsa is located 15 km&nbsp;southwest of the town of Polski Trambesh, renowned for its mineral baths and 40 km north-west of Veliko Tarnovo. It&nbsp;has very good infrastructure. The area has ample opportunities for outdoor recreational activities such as fishing, hunting and hiking.</p> <p>&nbsp;</p> <p>We present to you partly renovated brick house with massive stone foundations, with total living area of 85 sqm. It is on one floor and offers big hallway/living room, kitchen, dining room, 2 bedrooms, bathroom and basement. The first floor offers kitchen with dining room, bedroom, bathroom, storage and basement. The house is in good condition, partly renovated, with UPVC windows and doors, and is for sale with the furnishers.</p> <p>&nbsp;</p> <p>The adjacent yard is 860 sqm, flat and very well maintained. Some of the characteristic features of this property are its stone fence, storages and off road parking. You can spend lovely moments with your friends and family there. The garden hosts also a lot of fruit trees and is perfect for growing vegetables. The property is water and electricity supplied and is easily accessible all year round. Don&rsquo;t miss out on the opportunity to buy this property at such an attractive price and turn it into a cosy home set within beautiful serene location with fresh air.&nbsp;</p> <p>&nbsp;</p> <p>The village has a grocery shop, caf&eacute;, restaurant, church, petrol station, medical centre with a GP and dentist, kindergarten, school, post office and a beautiful old church. &nbsp;There is a regular bus service to neighbouring villages.</p>
</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>House for sale in Karaivantsa, Dryanovo Municipality, Price 134000 EUR</title>
<link>https://www.yantrahomes.co.uk/en/property-House-for-sale-Karaivantsa-Dryanovo/id/5386032</link>
<description>
<![CDATA[ <img title="" src="https://files.yantrahomes.com/thumbs_active/32/thumb_99242.jpg" alt="" width="200" height="150" /><br/> ]]>
2023-06-06 18:02:46 <p>This property &nbsp;is situated in a picturesque mountain village, set in the heart of Dryanovo Balkan, a piece of paradise not yet spoilt by human activity. The village of Karaivantsa is just 6 km away from Dryanovo where you will find an assortment of restaurants and bars along with all the shops you would ever need. Also close are the larger towns of Gabrovo and Veliko Tarnovo &ndash; 17 km and 30 km away respectively.</p> <p>&nbsp;</p> <p>The house is completely renovated with solid stone foundations.&nbsp;Situated over three levels with a total living area of ​​189 sqm.&nbsp;The first floor has a large kitchen, dining room, big living room, bathroom and enclosed poarch. An&nbsp;internal wooden staircase leads to the second floor, which offers an entrance hall, 3 bedrooms, office, 2 bathrooms and a large wooden terrace with unique panoramic views of the mountains. Last floor offers an additional bedroom.</p> <p>&nbsp;</p> <p>The property offers traditional wooden flooring, wooden ceilings,&nbsp; 5 ACs, central heating, UPC windows. For sale furnished and ready to move in. The house benefits from an excellent high speed internet connection. All you need&nbsp;to do is&nbsp;- put in your personal belongings and give this amazing property your own style and create a new home. Aternatively for those who are looking for an investment oportunity, the property is perfect for a small guest house with beautiful scenery, quite location and proximity of Veliko Tarnovo for entertainment.</p> <p>&nbsp;</p> <p>The garden of the property is a very large size being 2123 sqm.&nbsp;There is a big swimming pool, big stone barn, convenient for summer kitchen with BBQ.&nbsp;The property is enclosed by wooden fence, the access is through large gates, behind which there is a parking area.&nbsp;The garden is very well maintained, with a southern exposure and a hill view.</p> <p>&nbsp;</p> <p>The house is suitable for permanent living, since it is close to Dryanovo.&nbsp;Therefore, you can get a wonderful home with a large garden, which offers places for recreation, and you can enjoy the beauty of this heavenly place all at the same time.&nbsp;The property is located on the asphalt road, which virtually guarantees you easy access all year round.</p>
</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>House for sale in Gostilitsa, Dryanovo Municipality, Price 119950 EUR</title>
<link>https://www.yantrahomes.co.uk/en/property-House-for-sale-Gostilitsa-Dryanovo/id/5390064</link>
<description>
<![CDATA[ <img title="" src="https://files.yantrahomes.com/thumbs_active/28/thumb_98860.jpg" alt="" width="200" height="150" /><br/> ]]>
2023-05-12 20:17:06 <p>Gostilitsa, a village embraced by natures artistic touch, boasts a landscape adorned with rolling hills, picturesque hollows, and breath taking ravines. Majestic oak trees stand tall, enveloping the village in a cloak of tranquillity. Just a stone throw away, a woody pine forest awaits, inviting you to explore its hidden wonders. You will discover meadows, pastures, and agricultural fields that stretch as far as the eye can see, while the nearby River Yantra beckons fishing enthusiasts, hunters, and avid hikers to indulge in their passions.</p> <p>&nbsp;</p> <p>Perched atop an elevated position, the property grants you a vantage point above the village centre. Here, amidst the natural splendour, you will find not one, but two meticulously renovated houses sharing a generous plot of 1200 square meters. As you step inside the main house, a world of opulence unfolds before your eyes. A large master suite, complete with a dressing area and air conditioning for year-round comfort, awaits the fortunate owner. Two additional bedrooms and a bathroom offer ample space for family and guests. The luminous kitchen provides a canvas for culinary creativity, with ample room to transform it into a fully-fledged living kitchen. A downstairs cloakroom and a cosy living and dining room complete this haven of elegance. And let us not forget the inviting fireplace, perfect for those cosy evenings spent with loved ones.</p> <p>&nbsp;</p> <p>But that is not all. A charming two-story guest house awaits, presenting a delightful escape for visitors or an ideal opportunity for the savvy investor. With two living rooms, a kitchen, a bedroom, and a bathroom, this idyllic retreat offers breath taking views and two fireplaces, ensuring warmth and comfort throughout the year. This versatile space is perfect for those considering an Airbnb venture. Moreover, a fabulous bar, adorned with double doors that open onto the garden, provides an exquisite setting to unwind and entertain. And rest assured, convenient private parking is also at your disposal.</p> <p>&nbsp;</p> <p>Both houses have been meticulously maintained and are&nbsp;ready to move in&nbsp;and hold endless possibilities for enhancement and personalization. Your vision can truly come to life within these walls, allowing you to create a bespoke oasis tailored to your unique desires.</p> <p>&nbsp;</p> <p>Gostilitsa, beloved by expatriates and Bulgarians alike, boasts an array of amenities. From charming bars to local shops, everything you need is within reach. Excellent transportation connections to nearby towns such as Veliko Tarnovo, Dryanovo, Gabrovo, and Sevlievo ensure convenience and easy access throughout the year.</p> <p>&nbsp;</p> <p>In conclusion, this remarkable property in Gostilitsa embodies the epitome of luxury and tranquillity. Surrounded by nature masterpiece and offering two renovated houses with stunning mountain views, it presents an unparalleled opportunity for a life of fulfilment and relaxation. The allure of this Bulgarian gem is simply irresistible.</p>
</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>House for sale in Pavel, Polski Trambesh Municipality, Price 11850 EUR</title>
<link>https://www.yantrahomes.co.uk/en/property-House-for-sale-Pavel-Polski-Trambesh/id/5197020</link>
<description>
<![CDATA[ <img title="" src="https://files.yantrahomes.com/thumbs_active/25/thumb_98768.jpg" alt="" width="200" height="150" /><br/> ]]>
2023-04-29 12:12:28 <p>Pavel village is very conveniently located. It is just 3 km from the main road connecting Sofia and Ruse. The village also provides 3 grocery shops, 3 pubs, fishing dam, a town hall, a community centre, a school, a church, well-maintained village centre and asphalt streets. This is peaceful village with friendly locals and a great place to relocate.</p> <p>&nbsp;</p> <p>Arranged over two floors, the house provides 110 sqm of living area. First floor offers hallway, kitchen/diner, 2 bedrooms and bathroom. On the second floor will find balcony, hallway and two bedrooms. The house is with solid construction and needs minimum renovation to reveal its great potential. This home also benefits from an adjacent summer kitchen and has a security system.</p> <p>&nbsp;</p> <p>The garden to this property is 1500 sqm, flat and in good condition. There is a barn, and sheds. The fertile land lends itself to gardening, fruit and vegetable growing. The garden benefits of a water-well with pump. The property has water and electricity supply and is accessible all year round.</p> <p>&nbsp;</p> <p>Pavel village is situated 15 km from Polski Trambesh and 20 km from Svishtov. The area of the village is hilly and provides good conditions for hunting and fishing. There are a few natural reserves and a Thracian tomb you could visit.</p>
</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>House for sale in Stambolovo, Pavlikeni Municipality, Price 55000 EUR</title>
<link>https://www.yantrahomes.co.uk/en/property-House-for-sale-Stambolovo-Pavlikeni/id/5249035</link>
<description>
<![CDATA[ <img title="" src="https://files.yantrahomes.com/thumbs_active/18/thumb_99627.jpg" alt="" width="200" height="150" /><br/> ]]>
2023-03-18 12:51:20 <p>Besides shops, the village of Stambolovo has a train station, cafes, a kindergarten, a school, a church, a community centre and regular bus transport. It is situated 15 km from Alexander Stamboliyski reservoir, which has great spots for relaxation and fishing. The nearby town of Pavlikeni (just 3 km away) offers a modern spa centre, where you can enjoy a variety of spa and wellness procedures.</p> <p>&nbsp;</p> <p>This spacious property offers a total living area of 140 sqm distributed between 2 floors. In the main part of the house, you will find a covered porch, a hallway, 3 bedrooms, a bathroom and a store room. The extension of the house offers a covered porch, a kitchen a living room, a utility room, a wet room, a bedroom/dining room, a basement and a garage with an inspection pit. The property comes completely renovated and partly furnished. It has new plumbing and electrical system, UPVC windows and new appliances including a cooker, fridge/freezer and a washing machine.</p> <p>&nbsp;</p> <p>The garden is 1220 sqm, enclosed and easily manageable. It has some barns and sheds as well as a water well. There are also grape vines and mature trees. The property has a very nice location, it is close to a park and within walking distance to the village shops.</p> <p>&nbsp;</p> <p>The village of Stambolovo is 32 km from Veliko Tarnovo and 3 km from Pavlikeni. It is situated in the beautiful valley of the Rositsa River, which offers a number of opportunities for outings and outdoor activities.</p>
</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>House for sale in Stambolovo, Pavlikeni Municipality, Price 29900 EUR</title>
<link>https://www.yantrahomes.co.uk/en/property-House-for-sale-Stambolovo-Pavlikeni/id/5249034</link>
<description>
<![CDATA[ <img title="" src="https://files.yantrahomes.com/thumbs_active/17/thumb_99619.jpg" alt="" width="200" height="150" /><br/> ]]>
2023-03-18 11:52:18 <p>The village of Stambolovo is 32 km from Veliko Tarnovo and 6 km from Pavlikeni. It is situated in the beautiful valley of the Rositsa River, which offers a number of opportunities for outings and outdoor activities.</p> <p>&nbsp;</p> <p>This property offers a total living area of 97 sqm distributed between 2 floors. Ground floor offers kitchen, living room, bathroom and bedroom with lounge. The second floor is accessible vie external stairs and is distributed between hallway, 2 bedrooms, bathroom and balcony. The house is in proses of renovation, it has been rewired and had new plumbing installed. There are also new UPVC windows, new bathrooms and renovated roof. Just a few more touches and furnishers and will be ready to move in</p> <p>&nbsp;</p> <p>The garden is 1350 smq, fully fenced and with a water well and many outbuildings &ndash; sheds and big stone barn. The property has an extremely convenient location &ndash; it is close to the centre of the village. The house itself is very light and airy and would make an excellent home or a holiday house.</p> <p>&nbsp;</p> <p>The village has shops, train station, cafes, kindergarten, a school, a church, a community centre and regular bus transport. It is situated 15 km from Alexander Stamboliyski Reservoir, which has great spots for relaxation and fishing. The nearby town of Pavlikeni offers a modern spa centre, where you can enjoy a variety of spa and wellness procedures.</p>
</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>House for sale in Strahilovo, Polski Trambesh Municipality, Price 9000 EUR</title>
<link>https://www.yantrahomes.co.uk/en/property-House-for-sale-Strahilovo-Polski-Trambesh/id/5190039</link>
<description>
<![CDATA[ <img title="" src="https://files.yantrahomes.com/thumbs_active/16/thumb_98482.jpg" alt="" width="200" height="150" /><br/> ]]>
2023-03-11 13:35:22 <p>This property is located in Strahilovo, a village that is 45 min away from Veliko Tarnovo and only 10 min away from the town of Polski Trambesh where there is thermal bath and the water is said to have healing powers for pains. Strahilovo is a peaceful village, with an established community of expats, beautiful setting and lively atmosphere.</p> <p>&nbsp;</p> <p>We present to you a solid brick house with sound stone foundations. It is arranged on two floors, with total living area of 80 sqm. The first floor offers kitchen, dining room and living room. On the second floor where you will find a hallway, 2 bedrooms and a closet that is suitable for a bathroom. From the balcony you can enjoy lovely panoramic views. The house is in good general condition and after some renovation works it will turn into a lovely place to call a home, set in a peaceful and serene setting.</p> <p>&nbsp;</p> <p>The adjacent garden is 1230 sqm, level and well-kept. It hosts a stone barn, lean-to shelters and garage. The barn can be turned in a nice summer chill out area where you can spend the lazy summer afternoons with a book in hand. The fertile soil and the water well create excellent conditions for growing your own home vegetables. The house is water and electricity supplied. The property is located in a quiet and serene place, at the end of the village and has easy year round access.</p> <p>&nbsp;</p> <p>Strahilovo is a well-developed village with local shops and pubs, phone, TV and Internet connections, as well as regular shuttle bus transport to neighbouring town. There is a small river and a dam in the area, which create good conditions for fishing and recreation.&nbsp;The village has a community centre, elementary school and a kindergarten. A lovely place for your new home.</p>
</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Plot for sale in Gostilitsa, Dryanovo Municipality, Price 9800 EUR</title>
<link>https://www.yantrahomes.co.uk/en/property-Plot-for-sale-Gostilitsa-Dryanovo/id/5390061</link>
<description>
<![CDATA[ <img title="" src="https://files.yantrahomes.com/thumbs_active/11/thumb_98360.jpg" alt="" width="200" height="150" /><br/> ]]>
2023-02-24 18:48:15 <p>The village of Gostilitsa is situated in the picturesque valley of the Yantra, 36 km from Veliko Tarnovo and 15 km from Gabrovo. The location offers a variety of cultural and historical sites, one of which are the ruins of a Roman fort, just 2 km south of the village. The area also offers excellent conditions for hunting, fishing and hiking.</p> <p>&nbsp;</p> <p>This plot of land in regulation comes with the size of 840 sqm. The property is ideal for building a house, as it already hosts foundations of an old building of 78 sqm, which you could use in the construction of your future home. The plot offers sunny southern exposure and reveals terrific views to the Stara Planina and the valleys of the Yantra.</p> <p>&nbsp;</p> <p>The size of this plot allows you to have a beautiful garden with a swimming pool, barbecue and recreation areas. The property is close the village centre and the shop. There is water and electricity supply near the property, it is situated next to an asphalt road, which makes it easy to access all year round.</p> <p>&nbsp;</p> <p>This is an excellent opportunity to purchase a building plot of land in Bulgaria, in a magnificent location with picturesque nature, crisp mountain air and peace and quiet you have nоt experienced before. Go on and treat yourself with a home in the terrific Dryanovo Balkans!</p>
</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>House for sale in Strahilovo, Polski Trambesh Municipality, Price 34000 EUR</title>
<link>https://www.yantrahomes.co.uk/en/property-House-for-sale-Strahilovo-Polski-Trambesh/id/5190038</link>
<description>
<![CDATA[ <img title="" src="https://files.yantrahomes.com/thumbs_active/10/thumb_98732.jpg" alt="" width="200" height="150" /><br/> ]]>
2023-02-17 19:29:48 <p>This property is located in Strahilovo, a village that is 44 km from Veliko Tarnovo and only 8 km from the town of Polski Trambesh. Strahilovo is a peaceful village, with an established community of expats, beautiful setting and lively atmosphere.</p> <p>&nbsp;</p> <p>We offer you a wonderful, renovated, ready to live house. It is located on one floor and offers 100 sq.m. residential area. On the floor there are 2 corridors, a kitchen with a dining room, a living room, 2 bedrooms, a huge bathroom and a closet. One bedroom has a large walk-in closet and the other has a built-in wardrobe. The house is completely renovated and ready for living. It has insulation, PVC windows, new plumbing and electrical installations and a new roof. You can take advantage of the sunny south exposure and make a pool and barbecue with places to relax in the garden in front of the house.</p> <p>&nbsp;</p> <p>The yard is huge with a size of 4158 sq.m., level and in excellent condition. It has barns, sheds, an outdoor bathroom and a building suitable for a summer kitchen. The property is supplied with water, electricity and is easily accessible throughout the year via an asphalt road. The entire garden is fenced and there is only one neighbor nearby, which creates a sense of privacy and comfort. This property is ideal for your new home in a peaceful Bulgarian village.</p> <p>&nbsp;</p> <p>The village is large and developed, offering all basic amenities. It has a post office, a library, grocery shops, pubs, cable TV, good mobile network coverage and regular bus transport to Veliko Tarnovo and Svishtov. There is also a community centre, a primary school and kindergarten. Additionally a small river runs near the village and there is a dam, where you can go fishing.</p>
</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>House for sale in Ivancha, Polski Trambesh Municipality, Price 54950 EUR</title>
<link>https://www.yantrahomes.co.uk/en/property-House-for-sale-Ivancha-Polski-Trambesh/id/5194023</link>
<description>
<![CDATA[ <img title="" src="https://files.yantrahomes.com/thumbs_active/09/thumb_98733.jpg" alt="" width="200" height="150" /><br/> ]]>
2023-02-15 19:56:26 <p>The village of Ivancha is only 10 km away west of Polski Trambesh and 35 km away from Veliko Tarnovo. The village has all the necessary amenities and is water and electricity supplied. It benefits from a town hall, a post office, a community centre, a kindergarten, a restaurant, a pastry shop and grocery shops. There is regular public transport to the neighbouring villages and towns.</p> <p>&nbsp;</p> <p>We present to you a 2-storey house with total living area of 100 sqm. First floor offers kitchen, hallway, bathroom, living room, 2 bedrooms and storage room. Intern stairs lead to the second floor where you will find hallway, 2 bedrooms and terrace. The house is brick and very well-maintained, has PVC windows and some renovation has been already done inside, has central heating and is furnished. It features wooden floorings and ceilings. It only needs some minor touches and will be ready for you to move in and start living your Bulgarian dream.</p> <p>&nbsp;</p> <p>The&nbsp;plot to the house is big - 2000 sqm, leveled and well-kept. The garden hosts 2 big stone barns (one of which is used as garage), sheds and &nbsp;BBQ area with a traditional hearth oven. You can convert one of the buildings into a summer recreational area where you can relax and unwind or invite friends over for a party. The soil is very fertile and combined with the water well create the perfect conditions for you to grow your own tasty vegetables and fruits. The property is the property is set in a quiet and peaceful location.</p> <p>&nbsp;</p> <p>The region is well-known for its healing mineral springs and good quality agricultural land. North of the village runs the River Eliya suitable for fishing and family outings and picnics.</p>
</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>House for sale in Gostilitsa, Dryanovo Municipality, Price 11300 EUR</title>
<link>https://www.yantrahomes.co.uk/en/property-House-for-sale-Gostilitsa-Dryanovo/id/5390062</link>
<description>
<![CDATA[ <img title="" src="https://files.yantrahomes.com/thumbs_active/06/thumb_98224.jpg" alt="" width="200" height="150" /><br/> ]]>
2023-02-11 13:29:39 <p>The village of Gostilitsa is situated in the picturesque valley of the Yantra, 36 km away from Veliko Tarnovo and 15 km away from Gabrovo. The location offers a variety of cultural and historical sites, one of which are the ruins of a Roman fort, just 2 km south of the village. The area also offers excellent conditions for hunting, fishing and hiking.</p> <p>&nbsp;</p> <p>We present to you a 2-storey traditional style house for major renovation. It has total living area if 135 sqm distributed between two floors and additional small house attached to the big one. There are 4 bedrooms in total, one living room with kitchen, balcony and basement. You can either renovate this home or demolish it and put the materials into the construction of your new home..</p> <p>&nbsp;</p> <p>The size of this plot is 540 sqm.The property is enclosed by a&nbsp;solid stone wall, offering security and peace. The property is water and electricity supplied. It is situated in the center of the village and that makes it easily accessible all year round.</p> <p>&nbsp;</p> <p>This is an excellent opportunity to have a cozy house in a magnificent location with picturesque nature, crisp mountain air and peace and quiet you haven&rsquo;t experienced before. Go on, treat yourself to a home in the terrific Dryanovo Balkans!</p>
</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Plot for sale in Gostilitsa, Dryanovo Municipality, Price 29900 EUR</title>
<link>https://www.yantrahomes.co.uk/en/property-Plot-for-sale-Gostilitsa-Dryanovo/id/5390063</link>
<description>
<![CDATA[ <img title="" src="https://files.yantrahomes.com/thumbs_active/05/thumb_98220.jpg" alt="" width="200" height="150" /><br/> ]]>
2023-02-11 12:20:22 <p>This village can be found with breathtaking views of the Stara Planina Mountains, including Botev, the third&nbsp;highest peak in Bulgaria. The village is surrounded with un-spoilt nature and picturesque scenic views of pine tree and deciduous woodland, small vineyards and fauna and flora. Gostilitsa village is located within 30 minutes drive of Veliko Tarnovo and only 13km from Dryanovo town. The fresh air, peace and tranquility and the stunning views of mountains are truly breathtaking.</p> <p>&nbsp;</p> <p>Yantra Homes are offering to the market very big plot of land of 4117 sqm with wonderful panoramic views. The plot is ideal for building a house, as it has foundations from old buildings. 895 square meters of the plot are regulated, and the remaining 3222 square meters are not regulated. The property is supplied with electricity and water, the asphalt road is about 20 m from the plot. The large size of the plot gives you the possibility of a wonderful garden with a pool and a barbecue with places to relax. The exposure of the property provides incredible views of the Stara Planina and the Yantra River valley.</p> <p>&nbsp;</p> <p>The location and plot size is suitable for building a holiday home or building several smaller &ldquo;chalet&rdquo; type properties. Take advantage of this opportunity and purchase this plot of land with beautiful views on the edge of the village in a sheltered location with a Southerly aspect.</p>
</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Apartment for sale in Tryavna, Price 35800 EUR</title>
<link>https://www.yantrahomes.co.uk/en/property-Apartment-for-sale-Tryavna/id/5350069</link>
<description>
<![CDATA[ <img title="" src="https://files.yantrahomes.com/thumbs_active/04/thumb_98212.jpg" alt="" width="200" height="150" /><br/> ]]>
2023-02-11 11:40:43 <p>Tryavna is located at the foothills of the Balkan Mountains. A river with the same river runs through it. The town is well-developed, with regular transport links &ndash; there is a bus and train station with shuttle bus services to neighbouring towns and villages. It has a variety of shops, cafes, restaurants, hotels, guest houses, banks, etc. There are also kindergartens, primary and secondary schools, as well as a high-school.</p> <p>&nbsp;</p> <p>We offer you apartment for sale in a newly built resort, located in a quiet and quiet neighborhood of the town right by the lake. The apartment has an area of 48 sqm and is located on the first floor in a 4 storey block. The property offers a living room with kitchenette, bedroom, corridor and 1 bathroom. In the price are included laminate flooring and kitchen cupboards. The complex has a swimming pool, a restaurant, a conference room and&nbsp;playground for kids.</p> <p>&nbsp;</p> <p>Tryavna is one of the most beautiful Bulgarian towns, which has kept is authentic architecture from the 18th and 19th centuries. The area offers a number of opportunities for tourism and recreation. The town has a variety of sites and monuments to see, including the Popangelov House (the oldest architectural monument, preserved in the town), the Kachaunskata Mahala (a street, which is part of the architectural and historical reserve of Tryavna), St. George Church, St. Archangel Michael Church, the Museum of Asian and African Art, where you can see unique works from Tibet, Nepal, China and other countries.</p>
</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Apartment for sale in Tryavna, Price 38800 EUR</title>
<link>https://www.yantrahomes.co.uk/en/property-Apartment-for-sale-Tryavna/id/5350067</link>
<description>
<![CDATA[ <img title="" src="https://files.yantrahomes.com/thumbs_active/02/thumb_98177.jpg" alt="" width="200" height="150" /><br/> ]]>
2023-02-04 14:26:09 <p>Tryavna is located at the foothills of the Balkan Mountains. A river with the same river runs through it. The town is well-developed, with regular transport links &ndash; there is a bus and train station with shuttle bus services to neighbouring towns and villages. It has a variety of shops, cafes, restaurants, hotels, guest houses, banks, etc. There are also kindergartens, primary and secondary schools, as well as a high-school.</p> <p>&nbsp;</p> <p>We offer you apartment for sale in a newly built resort, located in a quiet and quiet neighborhood of the town right by the lake. The apartment has an area of 45 sqm (5 of which common parts), it is located on the first residential floor in a 4 storey block. The property offers a spacious room with kitchenette, a corridor, 1 bathroom and big balcony. In the price are included laminate flooring and kitchen cupboards. The complex has a swimming pool, a restaurant, a conference room and a kids playground. There is an option to use spa procedures too, which makes the apartment a very good rental investment as well, with all year round easy access and parking nearby. For all nature lovers, an eco-trail to Bozhentsi cabin starts from the forest behind the complex and the walk takes about 40 minutes.</p> <p>&nbsp;</p> <p>Tryavna is one of the most beautiful Bulgarian towns, which has kept is authentic architecture from the 18th and 19th centuries. The area offers a number of opportunities for tourism and recreation. The town has a variety of sites and monuments to see, including the Popangelov House (the oldest architectural monument, preserved in the town), the Kachaunskata Mahala (a street, which is part of the architectural and historical reserve of Tryavna), St. George Church, St. Archangel Michael Church, the Museum of Asian and African Art, where you can see unique works from Tibet, Nepal, China and other countries.</p>
</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Apartment for sale in Tryavna, Price 56900 EUR</title>
<link>https://www.yantrahomes.co.uk/en/property-Apartment-for-sale-Tryavna/id/5350068</link>
<description>
<![CDATA[ <img title="" src="https://files.yantrahomes.com/thumbs_active/01/thumb_98168.jpg" alt="" width="200" height="150" /><br/> ]]>
2023-02-04 13:39:12 <p>Tryavna is located at the foothills of the Balkan Mountains. A river with the same&nbsp;name runs through it. The town is well-developed, with regular transport links &ndash; there is a bus and train station with shuttle bus services to neighbouring towns and villages. It has a variety of shops, cafes, restaurants, hotels, guest houses, banks, etc. There are also kindergartens, primary and secondary schools, as well as a high-school.</p> <p>&nbsp;</p> <p>We offer you spacious apartment for sale in a newly built resort, located in a quiet and&nbsp;peaceful neighborhood of the town right by the lake. The apartment has an area of 71 sqm (7.5 of which common parts), it is located on the first residential floor in a 4 storey block. The property offers a spacious living room, a corridor, 1 bedroom, 1 bathroom and a big balcony with stunning panoramic views. The complex has a swimming pool, a restaurant, a conference room and a kids playground. It offers spa procedures which makes the apartment also a good investment with rental potential. It has all year round access and easy parking nearby. For all who love outdoor activities, you can walk the eco-trail to Bozhentsi cabin in around 40 minutes starting in the forrest behind the complex.</p> <p>&nbsp;</p> <p>Tryavna is one of the most beautiful Bulgarian towns, which has kept is authentic architecture from the 18th and 19th centuries. The area offers a number of opportunities for tourism and recreation. The town has a variety of sites and monuments to see, including the Popangelov House (the oldest architectural monument, preserved in the town), the Kachaunskata Mahala (a street, which is part of the architectural and historical reserve of Tryavna), St. George Church, St. Archangel Michael Church, the Museum of Asian and African Art, where you can see unique works from Tibet, Nepal, China and other countries.</p>
</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>House for sale in Varusha, Veliko Tarnovo Town Municipality, Price 199900 EUR</title>
<link>https://www.yantrahomes.co.uk/en/property-House-for-sale-Varusha-Veliko-Tarnovo-Town/id/50001255</link>
<description>
<![CDATA[ <img title="" src="https://files.yantrahomes.com/thumbs_active/00/thumb_98833.jpg" alt="" width="200" height="150" /><br/> ]]>
2023-01-28 13:58:28 <p>This Veliko Tarnovo property is located in the peaceful neighbourhood of Varusha &ndash; a popular residential area for those seeking to be in a city and yet away from its hustle and bustle. The house is just minutes away from the city centre and close to all amenities. The area offers a variety of historical and natural sightseeing.</p> <p>&nbsp;</p> <p>This 4-floor home has a living area of 212 sqm. The ground floor is a self-continent studio with option for bathroom. The first floor offers big open space living room with kitchen and dining area, there is also a hallway and bathroom. An internal staircase leads to the second floor, which features two bedrooms, bathroom and a balcony offering stunning views towards the town. The attic space is big and high enough to be accommodated as additional bedroom with bath.</p> <p>&nbsp;</p> <p>The house is in very good condition and was built in 2008, has PVC windows and doors, external insulation, security system and air conditioners. The property is fully furnished and is ready to move in. There is a small garden/patio area, where you can enjoy the peaceful area and fully relax.</p> <p>&nbsp;</p> <p>Another great feature of this house is its location. You have the opportunity to live in a quiet neighbourhood, still have quick and easy access to downtown, as well as have all the amenities nearby &ndash; a variety of shops, pubs, restaurants, shopping centres and regular public transport. This offer is definitely not to be missed.</p> <p>&nbsp;</p> <h1><strong>VIEWING STRICTLY BY APPOINTMENT ONLY!</strong></h1>
</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>House for sale in Dryanovo, Price 17000 EUR</title>
<link>https://www.yantrahomes.co.uk/en/property-House-for-sale-Dryanovo/id/5370073</link>
<description>
<![CDATA[ <img title="" src="https://files.yantrahomes.com/thumbs_active/98/thumb_98114.jpg" alt="" width="200" height="150" /><br/> ]]>
2023-01-21 14:46:57 <p>The neighbourhood of Tsinga is located just 3 km away from the centre of Dryanovo and some 30 km away from the historic town of Veliko Tarnovo. The property is set in a peaceful and quiet area. Dryanovo is located at the foothills of the Central Balkan Mountains, on both banks of Dryanovska River. The town is nestled in area with outstandingly beautiful nature with fresh air and magnificent views.</p> <p>&nbsp;</p> <p>We present to you a 2-storey house with total living area of 170 sqm. The first floor features a hall, kitchen-diner, basement and living room, suitable for shop or a bar. The second floor offers a hall, 3 bedrooms and closet, that easily can be converted into bathroom.The house needs renovation works before it is ready to move in but after that it will transform into your cosy new home in beautiful Bulgaria. It also can be done into small hotel/guest house business. This neighborhood is extremely close to Dryanovo monastery, Bacho Kiro cave and Dryanovo horse riding complex.</p> <p>&nbsp;</p> <p>The adjacent garden is &nbsp;924 sqm. In the garden there are solid walls of an old building, that can be renovated and made into a summer kitchen with barbeque and recreation area, where you can enjoy the great panoramic views. The property is located on an asphalt road so it is easily accessible throughout the year.</p> <p>&nbsp;</p> <p>This property provides comfort, peace and quiet. This is the perfect place for a holiday home where you can enjoy a peaceful life in a stunning setting. Dryanovo has a good infrastructure and offers all necessary amenities such as schools, kindergartens, nursery, hospital and medical centers. There are many hotels, restaurants, bars and taverns in Dryanovo, since the area attracts a number of tourists each year.</p>
</description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>